# **BATOUL AL-IBRAHEM**

Banias, Tartous, Syria | batoulab268@gmail.com | +963 932 763 995 | LinkedIn | GitHub | Portfolio

### **SUMMARY**

Software engineer specialized in front-end development, with extensive experience in designing and building web applications using React. Focused on transforming creative ideas into interactive interfaces, and believes in the importance of collaboration and continuous improvement in the field.

#### **TECHNICAL SKILLS -**

- Next Js
- Redux
- React JS
- TypeScript
- JavaScript
- Tailwind CSS
- Bootstrap
- Rest Api

- WebSocket-Real time
  - iqA
- Git GitHub
- From Figma to Code
- Sass
- HTML 5 / CSS 3
- C++ / Java
- OOP

#### **PROJECTS**

- 1. Al Blog Website (GitHub: Graduation-Project | Live Demo: Graduation-Project/)
  Al Blog using React, Redux, TypeScript and TailwindCss during my training at Focal X.
- 2. Tours to Tuscany Website (GitHub: task7-tours)

Tours Website using Next.js, TypeScript and TailwindCss during my training at Focal X.

3. Blog (GitHub: <u>task6-blog</u> | Live Demo: <u>task6-blog/</u>)

Blog using React, Redux and Tailwind during my training at Focal X.

4. Products site (GitHub: task5-crud)

A site that displays products and can be viewed, edited and deleted using Rest Api and crud operations during my training at Focal X.

5. Landing page (GitHub: task4-medicio | Live Demo: task4-medicio/)

Landing page design for medicio website using bootstrap and react during my training at Focal X.

6. Landing page (GitHub: task3-villa | Live Demo: task3-villa/ )

Multi page site for villas using react during my training at Focal X.

7. **Design 3 template:** (GitHub: Kasper <u>template-kasper</u> - Elzero <u>Template-Elzero</u> - Dashboard <u>React-Dashboard</u>) using only html and css.

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

Intern at Focal X agency as a Front-End Developer (React)

1/8/2024 - Present

Experience in designing and developing websites (Front-end) using Html, Css, Javascript and React. 2022 – Present

## **EDUCATION** -

Master in Web Science (MWS)

15/7/2024 - Present

Studying at the Syrian Virtual University

# **Bachelor Degree in Informatics Engineering (IT)**

2019 - 2023

Major: Software Engineer

Tishreen University, Latakia, Syria

• Achievement: Graduation from the College of Informatics Engineering with a very good graduation rate 78.73%

LANGUAGE -

**Arabic**: Native proficiency **English**: Middle (B2 level)